

Rodrigo

Developer



14 July 1983



Londrina - PR, Brazil



+55 43 999-108-629



http://goo.gl/F2v0o5



rodfersou@gmail.com

About me -

I am passionate about the art of creating computer programs.

As you can see by looking at my experience, I worry much more about building a solid foundation of knowledge than work just with a particular language. I consider myself able to accept the challenge of working in any environment, language, database or platform.

Design Patterns

Javascript

Python

CSharp

Delphi

Java

CSS

SOL

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

interests

Good challenges, which demand concentration and focus on quality deliveries.

education

2011-2012 Web Development Specialization course. **UTFPR** Use of offline web pages in the inventory of assets process. 2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course. UEL Generating code from a class diagram to an object-relational mapper. 2002-2006 Computer Engineering Graduation. UNOPAR Adaptive assistant to access classroom tools. 2000-2001 Data Processing Technical course. **CEETEPS** Development of a library management system.

experience	
2015-Atual	Team leader Simples Consultoria Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2014-2015	Software architect Anicet Corporação Analysis and development of big data systems and generation of market- ing information for e-commerce. (Python / MongoDB)
2012-2014	Developer AVADORA digital Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2013-2014	Systems Analyst AGILI Softwares para Área Pública Analysis and development of systems and web portals. (CSharp / Oracle)
2011-2012	Senior Systems Analyst MÓDULOS RECAP SOFTWARE LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for tire retreaders. (Delphi / Firebird)
2011-2011	ABAP Developer PADO SA INDUST. COMERCIAL E IMPORTADORA Customization of SAP ERP screens and reports. (ABAP)
2009-2011	Systems Analyst Maxwell Bohr Instrumentação Eletrônica Development of applications for automation devices. (Python / C / C $++$)
2009-2009	Systems Analyst ADVISE DO BRASIL Development and maintenance of application for automated processing of electronic texts. (Delphi / SQL Server)
2008-2009	Systems Analyst Development and maintenance of GPRS and Satellite messaging server. (CSharp / SQL Server)
2006-2008	Developer Amcor Flexibles Brasil LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for flexibles industry. (Progress 4GL)
2003-2006	Senior Systems Analyst Development and maintenance of ERP for vehicle dealers. (Progress 4GL)

languages

English Understand Well, Speak Well, Read Well, Write Well. Spanish Understand Well, Speak Reasonably, Read Reasonably, Write Little. Understand Reasonably, Speak Little, Read Little, Write Little. Japanese